<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Russell Rollins</title>
    <link>https://russellrollins.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Russell Rollins</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 19:30:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://russellrollins.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Not for Profit</title>
      <link>https://russellrollins.com/blog/not-for-profit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 19:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://russellrollins.com/blog/not-for-profit/</guid>
      <description>Not for Profit Recently, I was listening to the Conversations with Tyler podcast , and he had Stewart Brand on, who said something that stuck with me:
 &amp;ldquo;One of the things I’ve noticed all my life is that philanthropy should be the most creative thing going. It’s got to be more creative than government. It’s got to be more creative than anything the commercial entities can do. That it is not, is just a waste because, especially in America — we’re the most philanthropic society in the world, and yet it’s not as creative as it should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Twitter</title>
      <link>https://russellrollins.com/blog/twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jan 2022 16:07:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://russellrollins.com/blog/twitter/</guid>
      <description>The Bird Website One of my goals for the year is to learn to write better. I write technical bits and bobs at work but I&amp;rsquo;ve never really written for pleasure or for an audience of friends and acquaintances. Part of my plan to learn to write involves Twitter, Twitter is basically a multi-player game where you score points by writing. Seems like good practice. However, my use of Twitter has really dropped off in the past few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://russellrollins.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 12:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://russellrollins.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello, you’ve found your way to my blog somehow or another. Glad to have yah.
I’m a Lead Member of Technical Staff at Salesforce, working remotely from Atlanta, GA as a DevOps on the BREAD (Build Release Environments Automation &amp;amp; Deployment) Team. I write Go and Bash proficiently and I write Ruby, PHP, Java, and Javascript competently. But, like so many of us, I spend a lot of my time staring at YAML now instead.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
